https://www.kathamrita.org/privacy-policy

Jai Ma…Kali Ma…Jai Ma…HomeAboutMapPhoto GalleryContactMy AccountCheckoutHomeAboutM. (Mahendra Nath Gupta)Swami NityatmanandaSmt. Ishwar Devi GuptaProf. Dharm Pal GuptaShrinePublication ListBooksSri Sri Ramakrishna KathamritaM.,the Apostle and the EvangelistSri Ma Darshan (Hindi)Sri Ma Darshan (Bengali)Kathamrita Centenary MemorialNupurSmarikaDaily QuotesEventsShopKathamrita.org Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy was last modified on 15th March 2018Sri Ma Trust(“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates http://www.kathamrita.org/ (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.Information Collection And Use While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”). We shall ask information from You, which is the required Mandatory information as per Govt of India’s rules for Donation purposes. We shall not ask You any other extra information.Log Data Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.Cookies Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.Security The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Changes To This Privacy Policy Sri Ma Trust may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the details below;Administrative Office Address: Sri Ma Trust, 579, Sector 18-B Chandigarh, India – 160 018Email: SriMaTrust@Yahoo.Com Phone: 91-172-2724460 About Sri Ma TrustSri Ma Trust is a charitable and non-profit making organization engaged in propagating Indian culture with special emphasis on the life and teachings of Sri Ramakrishna Paramahansa and Sri M. Read more.. .ContactSri Ma Trust 579, Sector 18-B Chandigarh, India – 160 01810AM to 1PM, 3:30PM to 5:30PM Landline : 91-172-2724460 Mobile : +91-8427-999-572, +91-98153-30032 Email : SriMaTrust@Yahoo.ComConnect with usFacebookInstagramTwitter LegalTerms and Conditions & Privacy Policy
